firepips.com 2014-10-02

# Privacy Policy -

The FirePips.com (FP) takes the privacy of user data incredibly seriously. Please read the following to learn more about how FP ensures that your data is kept private and secure.

###  **What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers the manner in which FP collects and stores the personal information of users submitted at the time of registration. This policy applies to the user’s past use of FP products and services, in addition to information about the user which is personally identifiable. Such data would include the user’s name, address, email address, or phone number.

Please note that this policy does not cover the practices of companies that FP does not own or control, or to the employees, agents and/or representatives of said companies.

###  **Information Collection and Use**

FP collects information concerning the user upon registration for services and/or information offered through FP. Further, FP collects information about the user’s use of FP services and information, and the FP website.

Upon registration, the user will be asked to provide certain information, including name, email address, and phone numbers.

FP automatically receives and records information from the user’s browser in its server logs. Such information includes the user’s IP address, cookie information, and page requests.

FP uses the above identified information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content shown to the user; to fulfill requests for products and services; to improve the FP offering; to contact the user; and for the collation of market information.  
****

### **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

FP will never rent to, sell to, nor share personal information about the user with any third party, except to provide products or services specifically requested by the user, and with the user’s express permission, except under the following circumstances:

FP will, on occasion, provide the information to trusted partners who work on the behalf of or with FP under confidentiality agreements. Such companies may, from time to time, employ the user’s personal information to enable FP to effectively communicate with the user about products and/or services which may be of interest. At no point will said companies have any independent right to share this information; Where required by law, FP will respond to subpoenas, court orders, and/or any legal process. FP will also adopt necessary measures to establish or exercise its legal rights, or in defense of any legal claims initiated;

Where necessary, FP will share information with the relevant authorities in order to investigate, prevent, or take action against illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of FP’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.The transfer of user information may be necessitated following the merger or acquisition of FP with or by another company respectively. In this event, FP will advise users of such a transfer prior to the transfer of any user information. FP will also inform the user of any pertinent privacy policies subsequently governing the storage and use of their information.

FP may, from time to time, display targeted product and/or service advertisements based on the user’s personal information. Advertisers, including ad serving companies, may make assumptions about those users who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads resulting from targeting methods deployed.  
****

### **Cookies**

FP may set and access FP cookies on the user’s computer.FP may allow advertising companies to deploy and access their own tracking cookies on the user’s computer. Third party use of the advertiser’s tracking cookies is subject to the advertiser’s own privacy policies. At no stage will third party organizations receive access to FP’s tracking cookies.  
****

### **Confidentiality and Security**

FP will only share the user’s personal information with those employees who it is believed will require access to said information in order to effectively conduct their day to day responsibilities.

FP employs a range of physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in order to ensure that all user information is protected.  
****

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

FP may from time to time update this policy. Users will be advised of any significant changes in the handling of personal information through way of email, or by way of notice on the FP site.
